Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy last modified: April 12, 2024, 15:40:19, UTC.

The short version
-----------------

The TL;DR of the privacy Policy: I don't collect or share personal data.

The long version
----------------

For me it is of utmost importance that your personal privacy is respected. Privacy is important to me and I know it’s important to you, too.

The only personal data that I am processing, is that you have sent to me (by email for example). I do not collect personal data in any other way. I do not sell, nor shared personal data to anyone with the exception of what is required by law. Neither do I store personal data longer than necessary.

If not prohibited by law, I will inform you of any transfer of personal data when requested.

For your privacy, I am not either using any cookies, third-party requests, tools for analysing the web traffic or other means to collect or profile personal data. And I am not using any embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.) on this website. This is because embedded content from other websites may for example, collect data about you, use cookies and monitor your interaction with the embedded content.

I am using privacy enhanced technologies and configurations on this domain such as encryption of web traffic via [HTTPS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypertext_Transfer_Protocol_Secure), [HSTS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_Strict_Transport_Security#HSTS_mechanism_overview), [Content Security Policy](https://content-security-policy.com/) and [Referrer Policy](https://www.w3.org/TR/referrer-policy/) to protect your privacy. You can verify this domain privacy enhanced technologies and configurations on [Webbkoll](https://webbkoll.dataskydd.net/en/results?url=nikitin.photo) or [PrivacyScore](https://privacyscore.org/site/176469/). The usage of user-tracking technologies can be checked with [Blacklight](https://themarkup.org/blacklight?url=nikitin.photo). The security on the encryption used on the website can be verified by [Qualys](https://www.ssllabs.com/ssltest/analyze.html?d=nikitin.photo&hideResults=on).

I am using [One.com](https://www.one.com/en/info/privacy-policy) as host for this domain. One.com have their servers located in Denmark. I am also using [ProtonMail](https://protonmail.com/privacy-policy) as my email provider. ProtonMail have their servers located in Switzerland.

For the personal data that I am processing have I implement appropriate security measures and safeguards, designed to protect the personal data against unauthorised processing and unauthorised disclosure of (or access to) the personal data.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

All personal data is processing according to the [GDPR](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/HTML/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN). As I have no business activity, and all processing of personal data takes place only for a private purpose, recital 18 GDPR applies to this processing of personal data.

### Updating the Privacy Policy

Before updating the Privacy Policy, all person whose personal data I am processing will be notified.

Contact, questions or concerns
------------------------------

If you have any questions or concerns, please [contact](https://www.nikitin.photo/contact/) Niklas Nikitin, the owner of [nikitin.photo](https://www.nikitin.photo/).

* * *

All text and photographs are [Copyright](https://www.nikitin.photo/copyright/ "Copyright information") © 2011‑2024 [Niklas Nikitin](https://www.nikitin.photo/contact/ "Contact information"). All rights reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://www.nikitin.photo/privacy/ "Privacy policy").
